Serine Budd

Philadelphia, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Serine-Budd/578c0a9920cbe86e

Food service worker with a year and two months experience in food service, and a certificate in food service preparation and alcohol beverages. Knowing the difference between fine wine and beer. Preventing Signs of visual intoxication and signs of impairment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Guest Services Representative/ housekeeping

Extended Stay Of America - Philadelphia, PA - January 2015 to Present

checking in and out answering general question and taking modifying reservations, handle concierge duties and occasional housekeeping task,responsible for cash float through out your shift ensuring balance correctly at the end of the day, compute bills and payments,

Bistro

Marriot courtyard - Philadelphia, PA - February 2016 to March 2016

Greet guest, back of the house cooke, serve guest according to there number, take guest order, prep food for next shift, maintain a clean and safe environment for guest,

breakfast attendant

holiday inn suites hotel - Philadelphia, PA - November 2014 to January 2015

Greet customers with a smile.

Make sure all areas are clean And wipe down.

responsible for keeping buffet stock

responsible for preparing and serving

setting up and breaking down breakfast buffet

EDUCATION

ged

community learning center - Philadelphia, PA

SKILLS

customer service, adaptability, responsibilty, prep food, back of the house assistance, (1 year)

CERTIFICATIONS

food service

Serve all food and beverage orders efficiently using proper fine- dining techniques,

alcohol and beverages

Knowing the difference between wine, beer,

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Dedicated Team player
- Friendly and helpful
- Multi- task
- Customer oriented
- Fast and efficient worker Hospitality